Incoming groundbridge request... from Scotland.
环陆桥连接申请…来自苏格兰
Wheeljack, what happened?
千斤顶 出什么事了？
Where are the others?
其他人在哪儿？
Having a swell time taking the long way home in Ultra Magnus' boat, I'm sure.
在通天晓的飞船里享受长途旅行呢 我敢肯定
Miko included.
包括神子在内
I wondered what was taking so long with those sodas.
难怪她买瓶汽水需要这么久
Did you secure the Predacon bone?
你拿到巨狰狞的骸骨了吗？
The Beast Hunt kind of imploded, Doc.
这个…狩猎者们内讧了 大夫
Well, I just got wind of another 'Con hotspot. Right outside of Taos, New Mexico.
我刚刚又收到了一条虎子活动的消息 就在新墨西哥洲的陶斯城外
Since Prime's unit isn't back from oil country...
鉴于擎天柱的小分队还没从产油国回来…
Raf, set a bridge for Fowler's coordinates.
拉夫 把环陆桥指向福勒探员提供的坐标
You, roll with me.
你 跟我来
Not today, all right?
不去行不？
If you're all right sending me out there alone.
如果你放心我独自前往 那不去也罢
Alone's how I prefer to roll.
我就喜欢独来独往
Wheeljack, you do not want to make me abandon a complex equation to venture outside my comfort zone.
千斤顶 你要让我放下手头的繁重工作 去外面冒险吗？
Huh... Fine...
呃 好吧
But in case you haven't figured it out...
但要事先声明一下
I don't play well with others.
跟别人合作不是我的菜
Scrap.
该死！
Know what I love most about Vehicon troopers?
知道我最喜欢车型杂兵们哪一点吗？
They're easily distracted.
他们很容易走神
Ya!
走你！
Ha!
哈！
Huh!
喝！
You sure you weren't a Wrecker?
你确定你不是救援队的？
You sure you don't play well with others?
你确定合作不是你的菜？
Nice shooting, Tex.
打得漂亮 杰克！
Hey, Mom, what's up?
嗨 妈妈 有事吗？
Nurse Darby,
达比护士
what brings you here?
什么风把你给吹来了？
The medical supplies you so graciously offered to donate
你向我们慷慨捐赠的医药物资
that Jack keeps forgetting to bring home.
杰克总是忘记带回家
The hospital appreciates your generosity, Agent Fowler.
医院十分感激你的慷慨相助 福勒探员
Please, call me William.
叫我威廉就行了
Guys, I found a Predacon talon... in a museum.
伙计们 我在一个博物馆里找到了巨狰狞的爪子
Scientists were totally stumped when they excavated it in 1922, so it's been in storage.
它1922年出土的时候让科学家们大伤脑筋 所以一直被收在仓库里
But we're fresh out of Beast Hunters.
但我们的野兽猎人都被派出去了
Heh... I didn't choose "emergency" as my vehicle mode for laughs.
好吧…我选择急救车辆为变形模式 可不是白给的
Not sure you need a 'Bot.
不一定非得汽车人出马嘛
Maybe you should all just wait for Optimus.
或许你们应该等擎天柱回来
I'll have you known, nurse Darby.
请注意 达比护士
I was an army Ranger and federal Agent for Unit-E three decades before I'd ever heard the name Optimus Prime.
在擎天柱出现前 我可是当了30年游骑兵和联邦特工的
I'm more than equipped to handle a milk run.
这类零风险公务对我来说小菜一碟
In fact, why don't you tag along?
其实 你也可以一起来的
Oh, I don't know about that.
哦 这不太好吧
Oh, a... absolutely not.
哦 绝对不行
Mom, I don't want you anywhere near anything 'Con. It's not...
妈妈 我可不想让你跟虎子有任何接触 这不…
Safe? Is my teenage son seriously going to tell me that its fine for him to travel all the way to Cybertron,
安全？我未成年的儿子真的想告诉我 他可以开心地跑去塞博特恩
but his mother can't be trusted to go on a... on a...
而他的老妈却不能参加那个…那个…
Milk run.
零风险公务
A milk run?
零风险公务？
No, I... it's just... you're lactose intolerant, and I...
不 我…我…你不是有乳糖不耐症吗？而我…
Come on, Agent Fowler.
我们走 福勒探员
Ah, you performed well, my pet.
啊 干得漂亮 我的爱宠
This will be a splendid contribution to the spawning of your Predacon brethren.
这将对巨狰狞队伍的壮大做出巨大的贡献
My liege, we've located another of Shockwave's Predacon energy signatures. Weak, but steady.
我的君王 我们找到了另一处 震荡波的巨狰狞能量信号 微弱但很稳定
Excellent.
好极了！
Knockout, do not return empty-handed.
击倒 不要空手回来见我
Me? Don't know the meaning of the word.
我？我的字典里没有这个字
Isn't "empty-handed" two words?
空手不是两个字吗？
You would know, or did your missing armor turn up?
瞧你能耐的 找回丢失的装甲了吗？
Why, you wheel-bound...
你这只会在地上爬的…
Starscream! You have failed me enough for one day.
红蜘蛛 你今天已经够让我失望的了
Assume the task of monitoring for Predacon energy signatures, at once!
回去继续搜索其他巨狰狞的能量信号 赶快！
Yes, my liege.
是 我的君王
I'm sure you'll find the gig as invigorating as I did, "Screamer".
你肯定会像我一样发现这份 工作能让你神清气爽 小红同学
Ah...
啊…
Shockwave has initiated the cloning process with the specimens gathered thus far.
震荡波已经开始用目前采集到的标本进行克隆了
The Predacon currently among us will be but the first of a new wave of beast machine super-soldiers.
这只巨狰狞 只不过是新一波超级野兽机器战士中的先锋而已
What are you lurking about for?
你在这里晃荡什么？
Get back to your kennel.
滚回你的狗窝去！
Ah!
啊！
Um!
呃！
Ah! You mindless brute, look what you've done!
啊！你这没脑子的畜牲 瞧你干得好事！
You're awfully quiet, Wheeljack.
你很安静啊 千斤顶
I've never been one for chitchat.
我向来不喜欢闲聊
Why do you pretend?
你为什么要假装呢？
If you really wanted to roll alone, you would've hit the open road today. But you didn't.
如果你真想单干 今天早就闪人了 但是你没有
You called for a 'bridge back to base.
你乘坐环陆桥返回了基地
Hey. Don't assume you know me.
嘿！别自作聪明了
I'm not assuming.
我没有
Now, care to chitchat about what happened out there?
现在 可以聊聊到底发生了什么事吗？
What did I tell you? Milk run.
我怎么说来着 零风险公务
With one cranky cow.
是啊 就是那家伙的脾气有点古怪
The curator? Acted like he was guarding the Mona Lisa, instead of some prehistoric lug nut that's been gathering dust since Harding was president.
馆长？好像他看管的是蒙娜丽莎 而不是从哈丁时期就被尘封的史前螺母似的
I have to say, Agent Fowler, you handled him well.
我得说 福勒探员 你处理得当
I was quite impressed.
我很钦佩
Nurse Darby, I'd say that puts you one step ahead of my ex.
达比护士 依我说你比我前妻要更为出色
Hmm. Divorced, huh?
嗯 离婚了 是吧？
Ah... Yeah. What about you?
啊…是的 你呢？
What's the story with Mr. Darby?
和达比先生之间有什么故事？
Ah... More like a saga,
嗯…说起来更像是个传奇故事
but one I'm sure you've heard before.
不过…你肯定听过类似的
I have a bone to pick with both of you.
我是来帮你们两个鸡蛋挑骨头的
Run!
快跑！
Kick back, relax, and enjoy the scenery.
平静 放松 欣赏下风景吧！
Knockout to Lord Megatron.
击倒呼叫威震天陛下！
I have secured one vintage Predacon talon, plus two of the Autobots' pets
古代巨狰狞的爪子已经到手 附赠两个汽车人的宠物
for you to employ as hostages, lab experiments, well anyway you see fit,
您拿去当人质也好 做实验也罢 总之随您的便
so go on, Big M, tell me you love me more than Starscream.
所以赶紧地 老大 说您爱人家胜过红蜘蛛
My liege? Hello? Too familiar?
君王？呃…我太放肆了？
The primitive mutt demolishes our entire communications network
这只原始的杂种狗破坏了我们整个通讯网络
and lord Megatron intends to breed more of it?
而威震天陛下还打算要繁殖更多的？
Would you two hurry? I want this fixed before our Master is bothered by such distracting minutiae.
你们俩能快点吗？ 要在我们的主人为这些小事伤脑筋之前修好它
Entering access override code and rebooting now.
现在重置访问代码并重启…
Ah! No! No, no, no, no...!
啊！不 不不不不不不！
It's really taking them a while.
他们去了有好一阵了
Arcee and Wheeljack?
阿尔茜和千斤顶？
My Mom and Agent Fowler.
我妈妈和福勒探员
Hum... Maybe they stopped for dinner.
嗯 也许他们在途中共进晚餐呢
Isn't that what grown-ups do when they're dating?
大人拍拖时不就是这样吗？
It's what grown-ups do when they're hungry.
大人们是因为饿才这么做！
- Mom. - Guess again, Jack rabbit.
- 妈妈？ - 再猜 兔小子杰克！
and I hope you're not still thirsty because I'm bringing back something way cooler that sodas.
我希望你现在不渴了 因为我带回来的东西可比饮料酷多了！
I can't talk, Miko. I need to leave this line free.
我现在不能聊天 神子 我在等电话
Wait, don't hang up. Did Wheeljack show?
等下 先别挂 千斤顶回去了吗？
I think Bulkhead's really worried about him.
我想隔板很担心他
Wheeljack is fine. He's on a mission with Arcee.
千斤顶没事 他跟阿尔茜执行任务去了
Wheeljack's riding with a new partner already? That's cold.
千斤顶已经有新搭档了？太无情了！
What? No. It's just one mission, they're not partners.
什么？不 就是一个任务而已 不是搭档关系
Haha. I wondered how long it would take our two lone wolves to hook up.
哈哈 我一直在猜这两位独行侠什么时候能来电
I told you we should have waited for Optimus.
我都说了我们应该等擎天柱
There it is. The "I told you so."
到底还是说了 “我不是跟你说过了吗”
Well, no sale, sister. The 'Con was at the museum.
反正 我不买账 这个虎子就守在博物馆那儿
If we had waited, he would have snagged the talon before Prime got there.
如果我们等的话 在擎天柱到达之前他就把爪子抢到手了
And given our current situation, what difference would that have made?
就我们现在所处的局面 那又有什么不同？
Hello? How long have you two been dating? Because you bicker like an old married couple.
喂！你们两个拍拖有多久了？ 这吵起架来就跟老夫老妻似的
What?
什么？
We're not dating.
我们没拍拖
Frankly, I find it repulsive,
说老实话 我觉得那很恶心唉！
the whole idea of you fleshies... interfacing...[shivers]
你们这些肉虫…结合的整个概念都…妈呀哎
Knockout to base, requesting pick up, again...
击倒呼叫基地 再次请求 接我回家！
All right, is anyone up there receiving me?!
好吧 到底有没有人在听啊？
Nurse Darby. June.
达比护士 琼
If this 'Con gets us to Megatron's warship, the chances of the 'bots ever finding us
如果这个虎子把我们带到威震天的老窝 汽车人找到我们的机率
decrease a thousand fold.
恐怕连千分之一都不到
Never let a Decepticon take you to a second location.
永远不要让霸天虎把你带到别处去
He disarmed me back at the museum. Do you have anything we could use as a weapon?
在博物馆那儿我被缴了械 你有没有可以当作武器的东西？
Pepper spray?
胡椒粉喷雾剂？
On a 'Bot?
喷虎子？
Guys like 'Magnus...
像通天晓那样的家伙
I don't let them peel my paint. I peel theirs.
烦不到我头上 只有我烦他们的份儿
So if it isn't the new Commander who's grinding your gears, it's Bulkhead.
所以让你恼火的不是新指挥官 而是隔板
Hum... Just burns me up when a Wrecker goes soft.
呃…看到一个雷霆救援队员变得畏首畏尾 很是让人恼火
Look, Wheeljack. You'll always have the Wreckers as you knew them, in here.
听着 千斤顶 在你心中雷霆救援队永远都是老样子
Times change,
时代在变化
players come and go, and if you can't adapt, you'll rust,
铁打的营盘流水的兵 如果你不能适应 便无法生存
like the bones we're digging for.
就像我们正在挖的骨头一样
Don't push Bulkhead away. If something happened to him, you'd never forgive yourself.
别跟隔板疏远了 如果他出了事 你永远都不会原谅自己的
Trust me, I know.
相信我 我深有体会
Knockout to base, requesting groundbridge for the umpteenth time.
击倒呼叫基地 请求环陆桥 第N次呼叫了
Come in, base.
基地 请回复
Ohh. I can't drive around all night...
啊 人家不能开一夜的车…
- what? - Oh!
…怎么？
Watch the rims!
注意轮圈！
Now!
趁现在！
Well, isn't that just grand?
很好 这可真是太帅了！
Ah! God do...
啊…上帝啊…
Did I say "grand"? I meant totally rude.
我说“帅”了吗？人家是说这可真是太无礼了！
Ahh! My optics!
啊！我的光学镜！
Oh! Are we playing a human game now?
哦 现在我们要玩人类的游戏吗？
Because I would be happy to teach you the Decepticon version: "hide-and-go-shriek". Ha ha ha!
因为我很愿意教你霸天虎的玩法――捉迷杀 哈哈哈！
June! June, where are you?
琼…琼…你在哪儿？
Aha!
啊哈！
All right, little lady, show yourself.
好了 小女人 出来吧
Or I turn the snappy dresser here into a sloppy stain on the tarmac.
不然我就把这个潮男变成柏油路上的一滩血水！
You've reached special Agent William Fowler. Leave a message at the star-spangled beep.
你已拨通了福勒探员 听到星条旗的哔哔声请留言
Straight to voicemail, just like Mom's cell.
直接跑到留言了 就像妈妈的手机一样
Maybe they went to a movie?
也许他们去看电影了
Hum... Okay. Running from Bulk,
啊 好吧 逃避小隔
shutting down like that, pretty spineless of me.
拒绝通话 我真是个懦夫
On the bright side, you have plenty of backbone now.
往好处想 现在你骨头硬多了
Arcee, I need your help.
阿尔茜 我需要你帮忙
My Mom and Fowler may be in serious trouble.
我妈妈和福勒可能有大麻烦了
Last chance, she-human.
最后的机会 女人类
If you're not out here with my prize in 2.3 seconds, your boyfriend here...
如果你不拿着我的战利品在2.3秒内出现的话 你的男朋友…
Okay, first, not my boyfriend.
好 首先 他不是我男朋友
Ah!
啊…
And second, you're not laying a metal digit on him.
其次 你一根手指头也不能碰他
Not if you ever want to see your precious talon again.
要是你还想见到你宝贝爪子的话
- Where is it? - Leave her alone!
- 它在哪儿？ - 放开她！
I hid it on a train car. Let us go, and I'll tell you which one.
我把它藏在一截车厢里了 如果你放我们走 我就告诉你是哪一节
Try as you might, you can't con a 'Con.
班门弄斧 在欺诈的鼻祖面前
Fasten your seatbelts. It's going to be a bumpy ride.
系好安全带 前面的路会异常颠簸
Oh, wait, you can't unfasten your belts. My bad.
哦 对了 你们没法不系紧 我的错
Communications have been down for how long?!
通讯中断有多久了？
Soundwave practically has the dish repaired, Master.
声波就要把接收器修好了 主人
Which is all well and good for Soundwave, but for you...
对声波来说 这自然不在话下 而你…
Knockout to Lord Megatron, please, come in.
击倒呼叫威震天陛下 请回话！
See? All fixed.
看？完全修好了
Knockout, do you have the Predacon bone?
击倒 巨狰狞的骸骨到手没有？
In my sites, my liege. As are a pair of Autobots riding my rear.
在我视野之内 君王 就像在后面追赶我的两个汽车人一样
Understood. Just make sure you secure the specimen.
知道了 务必把标本弄到手
Now, in which train car would a Deceptive little human choose to bury a bone?
好 一个诡诈的小人类会把骨头藏在哪一节车厢里呢？
My money's on the convertible.
我赌它在敞篷的那节车里
Get Fowler and June!
去救福勒和琼！
Here's where you get out.
你们该下车了！
Lord Megatron, if a groundbridge doesn't open "tout de suite", your specimen will belong to the Autobots.
威震天陛下 要是还不快开环陆桥 你的标本就要归汽车人了！
Scrap.
该死！
Where are they?
他们在哪儿？
In back.
在后面
- Ah. - Whoo.
- 啊! - 呼!
Mom!
妈妈！
Are you all right?
你没事吧？
The milk run turned a little sour, but Bill and I are just fine.
无风险公务变成了高风险任务 但我和比尔都没事
Come on, June, sit down.
来 琼 坐下
Bill?
比尔？
Looks like you've been jacked, Jack,
看来你的位置被“顶”了 杰克
by another 'Jack.
被千斤顶
Bro-mance trumps romance.
兄弟情胜过浪漫情啊！
Glad to be your bro, bro.
真高兴做你的兄弟 兄弟
You have served me well today, Knockout.
你今天干得很出色 击倒
which is more than I can say for some.
比某个人强出不少
It was the beast that disrupted communications, my liege.
是那只畜牲扰乱通讯的 我的君王
I beg you to reconsider project Predacon.
我请求您重新考虑巨狰狞计划
The creature is incorrigible,
那东西不可救药
and void of all but the most rudimentary intelligence.
除了最基本的智能外 一无是处